- [Street Noise]
- [♪ Meaningful music]
[Security guard] Let’s go smoke a cigarette.
[Sound of door opening and closing]
"January Man"
[Sound of car door opening and closing]
[Meaningful sound effects]
[♪ Soaring music]
[Sound of footsteps echoing]
[Tense sound effect]
[bird chirping]
- [Woman 1] Father, cheer up.
- [Woman 2] Be sure to look for it.
[Seongwook’s father] Oh, thank you
[Woman 3] Hello, here
- Oh my! [Embarrassing sound]
- [Women] Take it.
- [Woman 3] Please find your son.
- [Woman 4’s laughter]
[Seongwook’s father] Oh, thank you
Oh my, this
- [Women] Oh, yes
- [Seongwook’s father] Yes, yes, yes
- [So Ryong] You came out early, father.
- [Seongwook’s father] Oh, you’re here?
Ah, let Seongwook find it.
They give you all this?
We too now
Reports started coming in.
[Sungwook’s father’s faint elasticity]
I guess the broadcast is good.
[Soryong] Hey, today I
Father, I have work to do.
A PD will film it.
While my father was handing out flyers
Because we will always be by your side
If you have anything to order
Make it easy
yes
[Sungwook’s father’s light smile]
[Seongwook’s father] Father
It must be really nice
I feel so reassured just by looking at it
how good
My father passed away
Oh my, this is my oh my
Oh my gosh, I did this...
[Limit] No, it's okay
Even when you're alive
Because he was someone I had no particular affection for.
[Seongwook’s father] Ah, yes
Well, that's right, oh my
- This, this...
- [Limit] Yes
[Prosecutor Lee in the video] You here
Did you install a hidden camera somewhere here?
- [Chewing sound]
- Trigger?
[Prosecutor Lee’s exasperated voice in the video]
- this…
- [Mute sound effect in video]
In front of the prosecutor, huh?
Are you reciting the charges?
커트
[키보드 조작음]
[한숨 쉬며] 아니, 지금 워딩이
'트리거 이 개새끼들'인데, 진짜
비속어는 못 써요
[기호] 아, 그니까
비슷하게라도 넣으랬잖아요
비슷하게라도
그래야 시청자들이 저 새끼가
얼마나 개새끼인지
- 직관적으로 알죠! kinda
- [Jiyun’s sigh]
[Jiyun’s sigh] Director
I'll just go with the previous version.
Let's go again
[Director Son] Oh my gosh
Aren’t you busy with the comprehensive programming?
Ah, Director
PD Kang, let me take a moment.
[Sound of footsteps moving away]
- [Coffee machine operating sound]
- [Sound of flowing water]
[Tapping sound]
[Coffee machine operation sound]
[Symbol] Director
As we know
It's broadcast today...
[Director Son] The busier it is
You have to take your time
- [Rattling sound]
- Even the invisible can be seen.
yes
[Director Son] Look,
I think it was from an interview with prosecutor Lee Jeong-geun.
Ah, yes, we again
Going to private events...
On the day of broadcast
I'm sorry for saying this
[Director Son] From the prosecution side
You look very uncomfortable
Just the interview with this prosecutor
How about taking it out?
Ah, that's the point of this broadcast.
Aside from that...
- This is what the boss instructed.
- [♪ Dark Music]
Oh, it's me, manager.
That, Choi Ho-seong, this incident.
From the beginning, the prosecutor
If you don't suspend the execution of the sentence, this...
What do I know?
[Director Son] I’ll say it again:
I just relayed what the boss said.
Sorry but
I'll pretend I didn't hear it.
Did you forget that you are a contract worker?
If you broadcast it as is
Kang PD starting tomorrow
This person is not here
Hey, Director, right now...
[Director Son] Instead
If only this broadcast ends well
KNS's first, probably?
really…
Really, as a full-time employee...
All I have to do is stamp the boss tomorrow.
[Director Son] Broadcasting from the beginning
I'm not asking you to make it again.
Without being specific
Let’s just skip the interview and this is it.
Let's live flexibly
[panicked breathing]
[Sound of door opening and closing]
[annoyed breathing]
[Jin Man’s light sigh]
[The former president sighs]
[Former President] The congressman said this
I thought he was a deeply religious person...
If I didn't have this, I would be so guilty
How did you even get into politics?
Who will be mayor of Seoul?
They said I was the only one
[Former President] Tomorrow
It's the day the candidates for the primary are announced.
Without a single text
If you just pray here
How do I know this?
Do I need to receive revelation from God?
Rep. Cho Jin-man
That's what women say
Why are there so many things sprinkled on it?
[Jinman] Article on preliminary primary election
A report came to us
Do you know how many there are?
[laughter]
- Either endure the aftermath.
- [♪ Dark Music]
Or safely
Let’s at least preserve the current position
The old boss chooses
One week
Looks clean, right?
[laughter]
So you always pray like this.
[Jin Man] Humility!
Who created that place?
You have to be humble
Shit, tsk
Take good care of yourself in the future.
Let's make a promise in 4 years.
Huh?
humility
[Sound of car door closing]
Can members of the National Assembly drive foreign cars?
-How good is the domestic car?
- [♪ Music that heightens tension]
- [Angrily breathing]
- [Sound of pounding]
[Rough breathing]
Look
It's sturdy
- [Sound of car door opening]
- [Jinwoo’s sound of strength]
[Jinwoo’s awkward laughter]
In Korea
There are a lot of cafes, right?
[Jinwoo] Ah, but this place also has charm.
Uh [awkward laughter]
Jinwoo Hwang
How did your week go?
Oh, well, what is it?
With my journalistic skills...
Did the old boss put it in?
[So-Ryong] You covered up in your face
Dr. Trigger
I thought it was the old boss
Haven't you tried it?
what? kid…
Hey, the old boss… Why boss?
I want to get rid of it no matter what
I guess there was a reason
Either me or the trigger
No, is this real?
Is it real or not?
Now I'm going to ring the bell of truth
[Soryong’s sigh]
[Jinwoo] Baby
A guy like me really
I need to meet a smart girl like you.
If I could make up for all my mistakes
I really like this recording
You can do more, baby
When did it end?
Are you going to sleep with me?
Mr. Soryong
[Jinwoo] Nu, noona can’t do that.
I hate my sister, I
- You can't do that, you can't do that.
- [Soryong’s Sigh]
[So-ryong] So
What is important information?
no… [sigh]
not that now
Have you ever heard the rumor about Hanju?
No, well, the rumor of the week
There must be one or two bad things
[♪ Meaningful music]
He, the chairman of our company
Taesoo Cho
They said he was dead
Chairman Cho Tae-soo
Dying?
[Jinwoo] Collapsed from a heart attack
It's been a while
Inheritance and company stock
Anyway, because of money
Everyone is hissing
No, a few days ago someone
Getting drunk and making a fuss
I heard you stole something
That's on the inside
There is talk about Jo Hae-won.
This makes sense
He was so drunk that he broke the window.
The thief who even stole the statue
Unless you are a relative
How can you be so quiet?
Statue?
[Jinwoo] Oh, why, you know
That one in our company lobby
- He took that.
- [Mobile phone operation sound]
Our Soryong says
That, Cha Seong-wook, that
I hope everything goes well
So with my last remaining innocence
I'm reporting everything now, really.
[Meaningful sound effects]
what on earth are you doing
Are you planning this?
Jo Haewon
[rattling sound]
[Seongwook’s father] No, this
- On the way...
- [Limit] Ah…
Ah, yes
- [Ratting sound]
- Uh, uh
[Hando] Father, you worked hard.
Go in and get some rest.
[Seongwook’s father] Yes, my gosh
Hey, maybe
The dog your son raised
Do you remember?
puppy?
My name is spring
Ah, spring, yes, spring
I've never actually seen it
I saw it because it was sent to me over the phone.
That was it.
Do you have that phone at that time?
Oh, well, well
Well, I took good care of it.
I haven't found it yet
Oh, with PD.
Even though I ransacked the entire house,
[Seongwook’s father] There wasn’t one, well, well
Let's look again
If it was used around that time
There might be something inside
There will be photos too.
Uh, yeah
While I was talking
I'll look for it one more time, okay?
Rather, in a conspicuous place
You may have left it
So, among the places I haven’t looked for
Let’s think about it carefully and look for it.
Ah…
[Mouse operation sound]
[♪ dark music]
translation
[Haru in the video is in Japanese] Spring is
What I told you was…
It was so terrible that I still remember it.
[In Korean] ‘It was like a ball’
[Heavy sound effect]
'It was like a ball'
[Limit] The owner
I heard it looked like a ball.
Cut off the corpse's head
Seeing damage
What if Bom witnessed it?
- [Rustling sound]
- [Spring’s howling sound]
[Spring roars]
[The sound of spring barking]
[Spring crackling sound]
- [Sound of refrigerator door closing]
- [Barking sound]
[Haru in the video is in Japanese]
Spring is in my eyes
The owner's appearance was like a 'ball'...
[Tense sound effect]
"Love Lee"
[♪ Music gradually heightens]
[Sound of carving]
[The sound of spring barking]
[Rough breathing]
[♪ Music fading]
[In Korean] Why are you watching this?
[♪ Meaningful music]
No way
[Limit] What kind of crazy person
Do you make something like this out of a human skull?
- It's not an unfounded brainstorm.
- [Picking sound]
That's because there's a writer I can point to.
[Hando] ‘Love Lee’, Mr. Sarang Lee?
[Soryong] Currently active in the United States
I'm a sculptor
just once
He is an artist who has held solo exhibitions.
Jo Hae-won, American name
'Lee' is my husband's last name.
[Hando’s surprised gasp]
You worked hard on the investigation.
Thanks to the informant
First of all, the pictures here
Collect as much as possible
[So-ryong] Let’s send it to Director Hwang.
When scanning in 3D appears,
Your face will appear soon
When the ‘January Man’ montage appears
I'll meet Jo Hae-won right away.
I collected the photos carefully
As urgent as possible
Deliver it to Director Hwang.
[Limit] Yes
[Sound of door opening and closing]
[Sigh of symbol]
[Sound of putting it down]
[Symbol] Ayu, Mr.
What's wrong?
[So-ryong] Uh, Kang Ki-ho
Did you finish the comprehensive episode well?
I'm finishing it
[So-ryong] Is there anything I can help you with?
Tell me now?
Don’t worry, we’ll broadcast without a hitch.
[Soryong’s sigh]
What are you doing? I'm not going fast
[Limit] Ah, yes
[Soryong’s sigh]
I'm just saying this just in case.
I can never be alone
When I go to meet that woman
Let's go together.
[Sound of footsteps moving away]
[Jiyoon] Hey
Without even getting permission from the team leader
Does it make sense to skip the interview?
[frustrated sigh]
What should I do?
Are you sending an SOS to writer Hong?
Oh, no, no.
Hey, I guess I told the team leader
I think it's right to say
They say it hasn't been completely removed yet.
I can't do that
He even corrects the script on his own.
I told you not to interfere!
It's directed by Kang Ki-ho.
In fact, the final editing authority
It's true that Kang Ki-ho has it.
you now
Are you siding with the amoeba?
[Jiyoon] Her trigger is her pride
I'm a kid who wants to throw away
Sister, not anyone else
Yes, amoeba, it's Kang Ki-ho.
[Mocha] Team leader, there’s a piece of gum
Are you really going to listen to what the director says?
I pretended to take it off while watching
It will go the way it was.
- [Sigh]
- [♪ Heavy music]
So I'm afraid the broadcast will collapse altogether.
Are you acting?
[Jiyun and Mocha sigh]
Kiho Kang
I'm not that crazy, really.
[Mocha] I must be crazy, really.
Kim Ji-yoon, this really won’t work out.
[Incredibly breathless] Oppa.
Listen to what the real head bastard says.
Just erase that, really.
I'm really breaking up with you
[Sound of intake of breath]
I guess I'm crazy
Don't you answer?
Do you acknowledge me as the director?
- [♪ Calm music]
- What?
In your eyes
Am I still a hot assistant director?
[absurd gasping sound]
I am the head of the department
They said they would change me to a full-time job.
[Siho] You and a stable person
You said you wanted to get married.
Among the same free people
No matter how well directed it is
They say it's not marriage
I really want to marry you
Huh?
I want to be recognized proudly
[Moka’s sigh]
[Sniffling sound]
[Seongwook’s father] Write, I clearly
I would have taken good care of it...
- [clattering sound]
- [Muttering sound]
Where…
Oh my, really
Where did you put it, huh?
I would have put it well
Ha, it's frustrating
- [surprised gasp]
- [Sound of picking up a moonshine]
Oh my!
this… [laughter]
No, wait, this is...
[Sungwook’s father’s sound of strength]
That… [Heavy breathing]
[♪ dark music]
Why do I…
[Sound of scribbling]
- Me, team leader.
- [Soryong] Huh? why?
It's nothing else, it's...
Regarding the last interview
I have one thing to tell you...
[Sound of clattering down]
Oh, that's not it
Because of the youngest writer
Ah
Uh, let’s start by posting an announcement.
Let's watch it together during the interview.
- Yes
- [So-ryong] Yes
Kiho Kang
I'm starting today.
See you at the office
[Awkward laughter]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
yes
yes?
[Police] You are not injured
We checked
Oh, what is that phone?
There was no major accident
I'm glad, really.
- Yes, thank you.
- [Seongwook’s father] Oh, thank you.
[Sound of door closing]
Hey, anything helps.
I don't know if you heard
[So-ryong] We will leave it to the company and try it.
I will definitely give it back to you, father.
uh
Even if it’s a photo of the dog you’re looking for.
I should come out
I said something unnecessary...
sorry
No, I found it thanks to PD Han.
[Seongwook’s father] I really
I put it somewhere easy to find.
If you didn't tell me
You probably didn't know
[Bell sound of a dog barking]
- Manner mode
- [Mobile phone alarm sound]
Is time up?
A little bit
-Excuse me, remote control...
- [Seongwook’s father] Uh, that…
No, well, today
Is there an important broadcast?
- [TV sound]
- Do you know Kang Ki-ho, father?
Why, saying ‘Father, Father’
A good assistant director who was chasing after me
[So-ryong] I was promoted to director today
The first broadcast you made
It's a day to show off
- Oh, really? Then I should watch it too.
- [Soryong’s light laughter]
[camera shutter sound]
- [♪ Nervous music on TV]
- [So-ryong] Oh, let’s do it.
[ticking sound]
[Sigh lightly]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[light sigh]
[shaking breathing]
- [Sound of door opening]
- [So-Ryong] Kang Ki-ho!
- [Sound of door closing]
- Where is Kang Ki-ho?
I'm here
you
[Soryong’s heavy breathing]
[Soryong] Who is it?
Who ordered it?
The boss goes through the general manager.
- so?
- [Symbol] removed
- You're not crazy, is this?
- [♪ Heavy music]
[Soryong] With your mouth
Did you say it or not?
Ho-seong Choi
If you don't stop this prosecutor,
Even if it goes on air
Nothing changes
What you said you would do with your mouth!
Did you pull it out from above?
The broadcast is over
Are you reporting now?
I was fine until the final episode.
How can you cut things like this?
The production you wanted so much to do
[Tapping] Your first work!
me tomorrow
Converted to full-time position
[Symbol] Team leader
Even if you tried hard, you couldn't do it
Just this one...
[Crying]
I'm starting a full-time job starting tomorrow.
Me on this broadcast
I didn't do anything wrong, just
just
As a director, please organize it a little bit.
I just did it, but why?
why… [shaking breathing]
The guy who rolled next to me for a year
Is that all you've learned so far?
[So Ryong] Directed by
It's a place of responsibility
It is the authority given to do so.
No matter what carrot the upper head throws
Rich and powerful bastards
No matter what external pressure is applied!
Hold on till the end and take responsibility!
authority to fold
[Sigh] I’ll ask again
Kiho Kang
In your debut work
Do you really have no regrets?
[sniffles]
[shaking breathing]
yes
I don't regret it
[Kiho sniffles]
[Sigh of symbol]
[Sound of door opening and closing]
[sigh]
[Tak]
[Soryong’s sigh]
[So-ryong] Actually, I
Kang Ki-ho, I understand.
I understand so much
But as a team leader [sigh]
I can never forgive you
bad guy
[Heavy breathing]
Ha…
I finally look like a person
[Limit] That’s how it was originally.
The world is not a flower garden
To the person I trusted
Being stabbed and betrayed
That's the reality we live in
[sigh]
A little bit
Do you trust me?
[laughter]
Why do you make people laugh?
Soryong Oh’s real character is
It's an inevitable flower garden.
People don't change
They say I can't change
[Feeding away]
Didn’t you see Kang Ki-ho?
- Why can’t I do it?
- [Limit’s Sigh]
It's not anyone else, it's PD Kang.
[Hando] If I had to say that, I would have done that.
[Angry breathing]
bad guy
Afterwards, the upper part of the head
Ah, Ki-ho Kang, Mr. Lee, tsk.
What hurts the most right now is
Neither the team leader nor I
[Limit] He is the party.
[after exhaling]
[Sound of placing a glass]
- I can't be with you because I have a bad taste in alcohol.
- [♪ Calm music]
[Limit] Oh, really, ah…
Team leader!
[Hando] Team leader
Team leader, I'll take you home.
[So-ryong] I’m alone
Let's get the spotlight
Do you know how to do this?
Trigger is a team!
What bad guys want most
Do you know what it is?
We fight among ourselves like this
Betray me and throw away my trust
It's ruined
One guy, one guy is full of flaws
As a team, it's worth a shot
So break your body
I didn't do it!
That bastard Kang Ki-ho says his heart hurts?
‘I’m so sorry’, you bastards
- [Car horn]
- [Rough breathing]
[Limit] Oh, it’s dangerous.
Come in...
[Soryong’s angry breathing]
Ah…
If you follow me, you will die.
[Sound of car door closing]
[Hando] Team leader
Team leader…
ah…
[sigh]
[♪ Calm music continues]
[Symbol] Team leader
Even if you tried hard, you couldn't do it
Just this one...
[Crying]
I'm starting a full-time job starting tomorrow.
[Meaningful sound effects]
[♪ Meaningful music with tension]
hello
[sigh]
In front of someone else’s house without an appointment
The reason why I came here so suddenly
What is it?
[So-ryong] What?
Are you here to threaten me?
Because it’s a nice day
I came to embroider
[So-ryong’s nervous breathing]
[Sound of clicking button]
[Soryong] IC
[Mobile phone operation sound]
[sigh]
sit down
[Haewon] It’s so fun
To live in this world
Mr. Oh So-ryong
He seems like a very serious person
What are you planning to embroider on me?
Mr. Oh So-ryong
Is Koo Koo Tae a different person?
20 years ago
I confessed in front of that person
I killed Cha Seong-wook
[♪ Soaring music]
[♪ Music with a sense of tension]
[Old President] Really
Did you kill Cha Seong-wook?
yes
Why did you kill him?
[So-ryong] To President Koo
They killed Cha Seong-wook.
Are you saying he confessed?
Mr. Oh So-ryong
Why are you so obsessed with Cha Sung-wook?
Were you a fan?
[absurd gasping sound]
Have you ever been caught on a fish bone?
well
The truth is
It's like a thorn in my neck
[Soryong] Even if I just swallow my saliva
It's scratchy and uncomfortable
I'm still in pain
No matter how much I don’t want to open my mouth
If you can't overcome your conscience
In the end, I have no choice but to vomit it out.
That's what the truth is
That's only for people with a conscience
I guess so.
[Soryong] What I do
It's about selling the reality of the truth.
[♪ Music gradually heightens]
Why did you kill him, Cha Seong-wook?
'why'?
[Heavy sound effect]
- [Emphasized sound effect]
- [Haewon] Why?
Why do you keep asking me why?
The reason is not me
That person has it
[Haewon’s Cry]
[Seongwook] Oh, what are you doing?
- Haewon
- [Haewon] Give it to me!
Oh, it's not really like that!
[Haewon’s grumbling sound]
[♪ Heavy sinking music]
Mr. Oh So-ryong
[Haewon] The person I believed was on my side
How did you feel when you betrayed me?
[♪ Calm music with a sense of tension]
Aren't you as angry and hurt as I am?
We
They look quite similar
[snapping sound]
[Feeding away]
- You guessed it wrong.
- [♪ Tension-tinged music]
[So-ryong] ‘Us’?
I'm different from you
I use the hurt as an excuse
I have no intention of killing anyone
In front of such a strict person
While wandering around
Feeling like begging for attention
There's no time to be lonely
‘January Man’
Aren’t you curious?
Is that also Jo Hae-won?
Sculpture in the lobby of Hanju Group
Bingo
[So Ryong] Author Love Lee
Where did you put it?
the statue
Mr. Oh So-ryong is looking for
That statue is
to our final destination
I kept it safe
[Haewon] So
Take a good look
We'll definitely see you again
[street noise]
[PD Seo] Team leader, is Kang Ki-ho real?
[Producer Yoon] Why?
What's going on with Kiho?
This guy says he's a full-time director as of today.
- [♪ Heavy music]
- [Producer Yoon] Yes?
I skipped that part of the test yesterday.
I thought I would get a lot of criticism, but
It's a shame because CP is on vacation.
No way
We all work hard
I came in after taking a test.
[Producer Choi] What kind of regular job is this?
Is it that easy?
- [Producer Yoon] But, among us
- [Jiyun’s sigh]
Filming and editing
There is no one who covers as well as Kiho.
What is a full-time job?
Not even Seonggol or Jingol.
Did the team leader know?
I'm asking you now
[Sighs] Yes, I knew.
I couldn't talk because I was busy.
[Producer Seo’s incredulous breathing]
[PD Seo] Oh, it’s too much, it’s too much
I probably slept late, but I came early.
Yeah, well, my eyes, my eyes opened
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[Mobile phone operation sound]
Father's old phone
The forensic results are out.
Already?
Director Hwang’s ‘January Man’
Not yet?
It's Monday now
The forensic company
Was yesterday Monday?
[Soryong] It was all the same weekend
Urgently to Director Hwang.
Are you sure you conveyed it accurately?
[sigh]
[Soryong’s sigh]
It's done
Take it and come down
[Sound of door opening and closing]
[Keyboard operation sound]
In the end, we too
You didn't tell the team leader.
Sister and now you're the main one
Don't talk behind my back, I'd rather fight
[Mocha] Like author Hong
- [Tak]
- Ha, really.
Ha, Mr.
[clunking sound]
[Keyboard operation sound]
[Sound of door opening and closing]
[♪ Interesting and heavy music]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[The vibration stops]
[Hakui] No
Villain setting or incident
Why are you so weak?
The person who came because name and color are triggers
[absurd gasping sound]
This is a play, a play
We need drama
Kill and tear
Provocative scenes must be included.
Are you saying kids can see it?
I don't even blink at most things
Kids these days
Don’t you watch dramas these days?
Really alive
A person who was torn to pieces and died
Have you seen it?
yes?
no
Only with fake blood and special makeup
Looking at it, you don't know it.
living with trauma
What about the real victims?
Every day is hell
[Writer Hong] To those people
Let alone healing
A drama about secondary harm
Make it?
[Laughing] Indeed
- [♪ Dark Music]
- [Hakui] This won’t work, man.
Hey there
Remove the trigger that doesn't work.
Just use what you're good at
I can't enter the workforce with that kind of mindset.
Oh, aren’t you a rookie here?
If you’re a rookie, act like a rookie
Just do what the experienced person tells you to do, okay?
Write again, one week
[Excited breathing]
Ugh
I even did this
Do I really need to tell you?
- [Author Hong’s exasperated breathing]
- [Sound of door opening and closing]
[Employee] Oh, that…
Author
Well, Director Jang
popular code
You point it out well.
[Author Hong’s exhale]
[Business employee] Photo of the dog you mentioned
It was there
[Soryong’s response]
[camera shutter sound]
I sent this to my boss right away.
I'll check if it's spring
[So-ryong] Oh
Anything other than this
Is there anything else?
[Company Employee] I’ve been looking for it.
There was a detective.
- [So-ryong] Detective?
- [Company Employee] Yes
Father's important message
Put in a separate storage box
I have a habit
I found it there, here.
[Response]
- 'Han Dong-hyuk'?
- [♪ Meaningful music]
[So-ryong] Among the detectives who played Cha Seong-wook
There was no name like Han Dong-hyuk.
[Limit] Why is this…
[So-ryong] Huh?
By 2006...
[So-ryong] Oh, maybe before that?
Have you had any text messages since then?
[Business employee] That's all the text message is.
[Soryong’s sigh]
[Hando] I have somewhere to stop by
I'll contact you later
[So-ryong] Ah, Handot!
[Doctor] Are you here to borrow money?
[Limit] Damn it
Have you ever lent it?
[Doctor] Why?
[Sigh] When my dad died in a car accident
I was wondering if you remember anything from that time.
crazy guy
What are you talking about in 2006?
I'm sitting there like it was yesterday
Because I don't remember anything
Didn't come this far
Memory isn't the problem
It's a defense mechanism
[Doctor] Because I don’t want you to remember
As if it never happened
Your brain erases itself
selective memory manipulation
Hey, teacher of anal surgery.
psychiatric care
I didn't come to get it
You asked about my dad.
smart eldest son
The one who was everything under the sky
What is there to remember?
[♪ Heavy music]
I got hit by a car that was being stabbed.
Everyone died
You're nineteen years old
Is that all you remember?
How did you get into Mensa, Mr.
I left behind two sons and babies just like when I was born.
Husband who died unexpectedly
[Han Do] Eoyu, what should I do?
A mother who cried and cried and then blacked out?
Done
[Han Do] As you know,
He was a great father, right?
Integrity and innocence
With just that pride
He used to be a detective.
Ha, Mr.
Only one team came to the funeral.
I won't forget you, you four
[♪ Heavy music continues]
[Tap sound]
[Detective 1] Oh my, you’ve had a hard time, man.
Maybe in your father's car
Is there anything that came out?
Mom said she already scrapped the car...
It seemed like there was something missing.
[Detective 2] That’s right
Why are you eating my family’s flesh?
You got punished, that bastard.
[Detective 1] Came out of the police station
Very smart but very handsome
Ah, the bastard who investigates drugs.
Why are you trampling on someone else’s team?
[Detective 3] Can you hear me?
Let's eat something
Do you think you're the only one hurt?
I'm haunted by that funeral forever
[Han Do-hyung] ‘I don’t make money like a detective’
'A job that is a disaster until death'
'Let's never do this'
‘Let’s do something that earns respect and makes money’
- I became a doctor with just that one trick.
- [Sound of hitting desk]
Isn't it you?
Tsk
why do i remember that day
Isn't there anything, Mr.
what did you do back then
You really don't remember?
[Limit] Uh
you were in the emergency room
[Hyung Han] Well, what do your aunts say?
Lying down next to my dark mother
Cool like a corpse
He said he slept for two days.
[Meaningful sound effects]
[sigh]
In my real dad's car
Did anything come out?
[Feeding away]
don't you know me?
[Han Do] Those bastards
Because you're unlucky, Mr.
What, what, just what, what
Roughly speaking, I’m just covering it up, well, tsk.
[♪ Interesting and meaningful music]
So what came out?
On the day of the accident
He said he got a call from his mom at the junkyard.
under the driver's foot mat
Because I have a briefcase
Take it
[Hando] But my mom
detective stuff
Say you don't even want to see me
He told me to go and burn it.
Tsk
But my father's blood is on it.
What is this
I couldn’t bear to do that.
[Han Do-hyung] On the morning of the accident
Dad told me
I said I had to go get something.
Well, I'm not sure.
[Sound of brother Hando taking a sip]
I wonder if it's important to my dad
I left it, just
[Hando’s sigh]
[♪ Meaningful music]
[Sound of paper turning]
[Grass bug crying]
[Sound of unfastening seat belt]
[Sound of car door closing]
[ECG meter beeping sound]
[Haewon’s sigh]
[Sound of approaching footsteps]
[ECG alarm sound]
[Increasing warning sound]
[Beep beeping rapidly]
[Long beep sound]
- [Cool sound effect]
- [Sudden beep sound]
[Beep sounds becoming clearer]
[ECG meter beeping sound]
I'm back, dad.
[♪ Dark and heavy music flows]
[Sound of approaching footsteps]
[Jinman] Hey, you crazy bitch.
When you come in, you have to say you came.
Why do you start with an axe?
What a mess, what a mess?
[Rough breathing]
[Sound of door slamming]
Our congressman
I guess you look a lot like the chairman.
[Feeding away]
They say they're doing it after 20 years
‘Looks like dad’?
[Chuckling]
I'm better, feel better, Mr. Lee
Are you still playing like that these days?
[♪ Music with a sense of tension]
Anything fun down there
Did you hide something?
If you're curious, let's go down together.
I'll play with you
Once upon a time
The one that came up alive from down there
you and me
Do you know that there are only two of us?
[Jinman laughs]
[Jinman] What am I talking about?
I have no idea
- [♪ Dark Music]
- [Haewon’s encouraging sound]
[Jinman’s sound of strength]
[Jinman’s angry voice]
[Haewon’s struggling sounds]
[Jinman gives strength] Lee, Lee
Oh, you crazy bitch
[clunking sound]
-You crazy bitch.
- [Haewon’s moans]
You crazy bitch
-You crazy bitch.
- [Haewon’s struggling sounds]
[Jinman’s sound of strength]
You crazy bitch
[light laughter]
You crazy bitch!
- [The spirit of liberation]
- [Punching sound]
[Haewon’s heavy breathing]
[Jinman moans]
[light laughter]
Ouch
[shaking breathing]
Ouch!
it hurts! You fucking bitch!
- [Jinman’s swearing sound]
- [cough]
- [Jinman’s sound of strength]
- [Pulling sound]
- [Jin Man’s painful scream]
- [Haewon’s labored breathing]
You crazy bitch!
suddenly appear
Why the hell, damn it!
[Painful breathing]
Did you run out of money?
I'll give you your share of dad's.
Eat and get out!
suddenly?
[Haewon] Always just for this moment
I've been dreaming and waiting for this, but suddenly?
- [Jin Man’s trembling breathing]
- Jinman, look at your sister.
My sister wants to get it
How hard have you been working so far?
[Whimpering] It hurts!
Never do that to your family
Don't you remember what your dad taught you?
[Jinman moans]
- [Haewon] Who
- [Jin Man’s trembling breathing]
- To whom
- [♪ Devotional and heavy music]
What did you teach?
you
You're a bigger bitch than your dad
[Jinman’s strong breathing]
- [Jinman’s moans]
- [Haewon’s heavy breathing]
So
Still alive
[Sound of intake of breath]
[Rough breathing]
It's been a while
[Frightened breathing]
All of my inheritance
There's a pledge to donate there.
[Jinman’s heavy breathing]
[Jinman] What? Are you donating?
[sigh]
Noblesse Oblige
Doesn't this idiot in politics even know that?
[Jinman laughs]
Soon to be deceased
Including the chairman's share
Donate up to half of your inheritance there.
[Sound of throwing business cards]
[Jinman] Because I’m begging you to be a disobedient person
I asked why it was like that
That's right, money in the end
[Jinman’s laughter]
What is the point of donating?
you made
I guess it could be a paper company?
But am I crazy?
But fuck
If you're going to mess with me, touch my dad.
Why are you touching mine?
A person with many years to live
[Jinman’s heavy breathing]
[Small] Are you okay?
If you dig one week properly from the trigger,
[Haewon] All of your things become pieces of tissue paper
They should even give up a gold badge.
Who touches Hanju?
Broadcast trigger?
[Chuckling]
[Laughing] This is ridiculous.
[♪ Heavy music continues]
[Jin Man’s trembling breathing]
Am I the only one who gets screwed?
너도 좆 돼
[옅은 한숨]
너에게 달려 있어
니가 좋아하는 인형 놀이
계속하고 싶으면
[쪽]
- [♪ 웅장하게 고조되는 음악]
- [문 여닫히는 소리]
미국에서 가만히 잘 사는 년을
괜히 들쑤셔 가지고
이 사달을 만들어
이 트리거 이 미친 새끼들은!
[cell phone vibrating sound]
- [♪ Dark Music]
- [Mobile phone operation sound]
Even the one remaining crown
I can’t let it get taken away.
[light laughter]
- [♪ Calm music flows]
- [Rattling sound]
[Symbol] Mochaya
[Sikho’s laughter]
You waited a long time, right?
[Mocha] No
[Sign's strengthening sound]
[light laughter]
Congratulations on becoming a full-time employee.
Wow, really
After all, there is only Pogong, huh?
I thought about it
The reason I liked you
Directing, assistant directing
[Mocha] Full-time employee
Well, it's not a name like this.
It was Kang Ki-ho himself.
i like money
Because I want to live a stable life
So
Life was always anxious and difficult
But our Kang Ki-ho was different.
[In a thirsty voice] To anyone
Friendly and
It's warm again
Even if you lose a little
Because I'm a person who doesn't care
- So I…
- [Symbol] Hey, Mocha.
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute
[Laughing slightly] Oh, wait a minute.
After everything passed, I realized
[♪ Calm and lonely music
Dayoung Da-young ‘This night will soon pass’]
As for regular workers,
It's not a requirement for my marriage.
[Mocha] Don’t be shaken
I should have caught it
I was wrong, sorry
[Symbol] Hug
[sniffles]
[In a trembling voice] Ah…
[In a thirsty voice] Hug, hug
Otherwise, Jin, you really regret it?
I already regret it
I'll go
[sniffling]
[Sobbing]
Who's in the celebration cake?
Are you writing a comment like this?
Me, you evil pup…
[Kiho’s sobbing sound]
[sigh]
[♪ Lonely music continues]
[In a drunken tone] Are you here, bro?
No, bro
Bbogong tells me to break up with him.
What should I do now?
If it's cut, it's over.
What should I do? [Sigh]
Huh?
My brother is cursing me in his mind right now, right?
‘Wow, you renegade bastard’
- [Hando’s absurd breathing sound]
- [Symbol] ‘It’s a subject that doesn’t even have an academic background’
'I became a full-time employee by selling broadcasting.
'You trash bastard'
[Limit] Someone said that before
'I want to shake up that group.
'Find the weakest link there'
Ah, the weakest link among us
Those guys who dug in are smart.
Oh, then you are on my side?
no
PD Kang’s real side is
It's just the team leader.
[Limit] While I was living in society,
The coolest person I've ever met
You know, our team leader.
[In a thirsty voice] I know best
[Laughing slightly] I am the team leader
When we first met...
Don't force your smile like that
[sniffles]
I have something to laugh about
Is it because there isn't much?
Who doesn't do anything like that?
I keep seeing you when you smile
[Hando] Because I wanted to cry
I don't think that's the case
[Crying breathing]
Without even thinking about it
Team leader, don’t hurt me
Come back now
[Sobbing]
[sigh]
[♪ Soaring lonely music]
When you cry like that, it makes me want to cry too
[Kiho’s sobbing sound]
[bird chirping]
[Hando] Let me introduce you to him.
Detective Han Dong-hyuk
This is my father
- [Seongwook’s father] Oh my
- [♪ Heavy music]
A place for my son to be
I found it
Our Seongwook
Maybe I can find it
We met just once like that
Because there is no contact
just
You came to me like that
I thought you were one of the detectives.
I never thought it would turn out like this
I never dreamed
[Sound of zipper opening]
In my father’s car that crashed in 2006
It was discovered.
[rustling sound]
[Limit] The four detectives here
Cha Seong-wook's death
I tried to cover it up
that
My father found out
[Emphasized sound effect]
This…
My father is like this.
[Limit] This document
It's definitely right
[Seongwook’s father is crying]
[Seongwook’s father sobs]
alternative
where is it
[Seongwook’s father] I searched for you so desperately.
Someone has already found you
[Seongwook continues to sob]
Oh my
[bird chirping]
The reason for the crash landing on the trigger
I thought I knew everything
I didn't know that
Did the team leader know?
I've been crash-landing for 10 years, too.
[♪ Meaningful music]
- [Hando laughs]
- [Mobile phone vibrating sound]
[So-ryong] Yes, Director Hwang
Did you get the results?
[Director Hwang] I sent you a photo of the statue.
Taken as a wireframe
I ran a scan
A montage of heads like that
An old photo of Cha Seong-wook
Match rate over 98%
[Soryong] Match rate
98%?
[Small] 98?
[Director Hwang] Yes
But the year this statue was made
After Cha Seong-wook disappeared
Didn't you?
Who on earth is the author who made this?
How did you make this example?
[Tense sound effect]
[♪ Music with a sense of tension]
[Eerie sound effect]
[Sound of carving]
[pop sound]
Now officially
I could interview Haewon Jo.
[Call connection tone]
[Mobile phone operation sound]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
tonight
Go to Jo Haewon’s studio
[Sound of fastening seat belt]
[♪ Nervous music]
[♪ Music stops]
- [Rough breathing echoing in the silence]
- [♪ Continuing tense music]
[The crackling sound becomes clearer]
[panicked breathing]
[Tense sound effect]
- [Eerie sound effect]
- [♪ Soaring music]
[Thumping sound effect]
[♪ Calm and lonely music
Dayoung Da-young ‘This night will soon pass’]
[bird chirping]
[Limit] Righteous and honest
I admit that I lived
Anyway
This wasn't it, right?
I was too young to know anything
To understand
Because he was such a distant person
I think I finally found a piece
[♪ Lonely music continues]